{
    "test": [
      {
       "question": "What's a cat?",
       "answer": "An animal!",
       "difficulty": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "What's a dog?",
        "answer": "An even better animal!",
        "difficulty": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Which fish is the fastest fish?",
        "answer": "Sailfish",
        "difficulty": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "Where was the Antikythera mechanism found?",
        "answer": "Off the coast of Antikythera",
        "difficulty": 3
      },
      {
         "question": "Who first circumnavigated the earth?",
         "answer": "Magellan",
         "difficulty": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the acronym DNA stand for?",
        "answer": "Deoxyribonucleic acid",
        "difficulty": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "Is Sweden a country?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "difficulty": 1
      },
			{
        "question": "What is Melissaâ€™s favorite baby animal?",
        "answer": "Cuttlefish",
        "difficulty": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "Is Australia a country or continent?",
        "answer": "Both",
        "difficulty": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Is 812393014421 divisible by 3?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "difficulty": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "What status code represents 'Page Not Found'?",
        "answer": "404",
        "difficulty": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a tomato a fruit or vegetable?",
        "answer": "Fruit",
        "difficulty": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "How many nodes are in a complete binary tree of height N?",
        "answer" : "(2^N)-1",
        "difficulty": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "In the description of biological cells, 'eukaryotes' are contrasted with these, which exist without a nucleus.",
        "answer" : "Prokaryotes",
        "difficulty": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "In biology, what is considered the 'powerhouse' of the cell?",
        "answer" : "Mitochondria",
        "difficulty": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "What does HTML stand for?",
        "answer" : "Hyper-text Markup Language",
        "difficulty": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Which WikiLeaks-aided former NSA contractor famously released classified military documents over the internet?",
        "answer" : "Edward Snowden",
        "difficulty": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "In what year did Apple release the iPad?",
        "answer" : "2010",
        "difficulty": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the full name of the small furry mammal known more commonly as 'coati'?",
        "answer" : "Coatimundi",
        "difficulty": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "What trivia gameshow famously answers questions in the form 'What is a ____'?",
        "answer" : "Jeopardy",
        "difficulty": 2
      }
    ]
  }
